看起来很好喝
Looks good.
你好
Hello.
你可以放下枪
You can lower that.
W代表着什么？
What's the W for?
这里的第一批移民
You know, the first settlers here,
他们悬赏狼头
they put bounties on wolves' heads.
找了印第安人
Brought the natives into it.
让他们猎狼
Made them hunt them.
没多久 狼就被杀光了
Didn't take them too long to kill them all.
狼现在回来了
They're back now.
有什么想法？
Thoughts?
天道好轮回
Everything gets a return.
- 你在耍嘴皮吗？- 我没有
- Are you shitting me? - No, I shit you not.
我喜欢这样
I like this.
聊聊天
Just talking.
我没什么机会见到新面孔
I don't get to meet new people very often.
大概每两周一次
Maybe once every two weeks.
- 真多 - 我很努力
- That's a lot. - Oh, I work at it.
我们都是
We do.
有时候我们找到营地 掳掠一番
Sometimes we find camps. We run through them.
但我们也会设陷阱
But we have traps, too.
那不一样 不是这样的见面
It's different. It's not like meeting like this.
平等地见面
As equals.
在火堆前跟陌生人聊聊天
Little chats in front of a fire with a stranger.
这是如今最像电影的东西了
That's the closest thing to movies now.
我很想念电影
I miss the movies.
我以前… 放下
I used to... put that down.
为什么？
Why?
因为我想要
Because I want it.
我想要你有的一切
I want everything you have.
每一滴
Every last drop.
我能留一点吗？
Can I keep a little of it?
让我挺过一两天？
Just to get me through a day or two?
让我活下来
You know, just to keep me alive?
我也要带走你
I'm taking you, too.
你可不会活着
And you're not exactly gonna be alive.
好吧
Okay.
这附近的一些印第安人部落
Some of the tribes around here,
他们认为第一批人类
they thought that the first people were wolves
是由狼变的
transformed into men.
现在
And now, well,
你知道
you know.
天道好轮回 对吧？
Everything gets a return, right?
我的补给和装备可以全归你
You can have my supplies. You can have everything.
没必要搞得太丑恶
Doesn't need to be any ugliness.
但我不能允许你带走我
But I can't allow you to take me away.
我不会允许的
I will not allow that.
别动
Don't move.
别乱动
Just be still.
你们快走吧
You should just go now.
不
No.
走吧
Just go.
拜托
Please.
动手
Now
《行尸走肉》
有什么好笑的？
What's so funny?
你一直都在这里吗？
You were here the whole time?
整晚都在
All night.
有什么好笑的？
What's so funny?
这就跟在车厢里一样
It's... it's like the train car.
发生了这么多事
After the whole thing,
我还被关在那里
I'm still there.
迪安娜想让你来这里 冷静一下
Deanna wanted you in here, calm things down.
罗西塔处理了你的伤口
Rosita patched you up.
卡尔来了一会儿
Carl came by for a while.
我让他回家了
I sent him home.
瑞克
Rick.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我们让皮特待在另一座房子里
We put Pete in another house.
你本可以告诉我家暴的事
You could have told me what was happening.
事情进展迅速 然后出了诺亚的事
It moved fast. And then Noah.
我不能跟你说枪的事
I couldn't tell you about the gun.
是啊
No, you couldn't.
你想待在这里
Oh, you wanted this place.
我们必须找个安身之地
We had to stop being out there.
我们到这里了
Well, we're here.
你刚说了你不在这里
Well, you just said you weren't.
你从哪里弄到的枪？
Where'd you get the gun?
你从武器库里拿的？对吧？
You took it, right? From the armory?
那真愚蠢 你为什么要这样做？
That was stupid. Why did you do it?
以防万一
Just in case.
迪安娜打算今晚开个会
Deanna's planning to have a meeting tonight.
想去的人都能参加
For anyone who wants to.
- 为了流放瑞克吗？- 她会提议的
- To kick Rick out? - To try.
我们并不确定
We don't know that.
玛姬现在和迪安娜在一起
Maggie's with Deanna right now.
她会搞清楚的
She's gonna find out what it is.
在会议上 你要说你担心
At the meeting, you say you were worried
有人遭受虐待
about someone being abused
而大家都坐视不管
and no one was doing anything about it.
你要说你拿了枪是为了保证
You say you took a gun just to be sure
那个袭击你的人不会伤害杰茜
that Jessie was safe from a man who wound up attacking you.
你说你会听他们处置
You say you'll do whatever you want them to.
编一个他们想听的故事就好
Just tell them a story that they want to hear.
我来这里之后就一直这样
That's what I've been doing since I got here.
为什么？
Why?
因为这些人是孩子
Because these people are children
孩子喜欢故事
and children like stories.
如果说尽好话
What happens after all the nice words
他们还想赶走他怎么办
and they still try to kick him out?
他们现在派人看守武器库了
They're guarding the armory now.
我们还有刀
We still have knives.
对付他们刀就够了
That's all we'll need against them.
今晚在会议上
Well, tonight at the meeting,
假如情况不妙
if it looks like it's going bad,
我就吹口哨
I whistle.
卡萝尔抓住迪安娜
Carol grabs Deanna,
我拿下斯宾塞
I take Spencer,
你抓住雷吉
you grab Reg,
格伦和亚伯拉罕掩护我们 控制人群
Glenn and Abraham cover us, watch the crowd.
我们可以和他们谈的
We can talk to them.
我们会谈的
Yeah, we will.
但是如果说不通
If we can't get through,
我们就抓三个他们的人
we take the three of them
说我们会割他们的喉
and say we'll slit their throats.
就像在终点站那样吗？
Like at Terminus?
不 我们只是说说而已
No, we just tell them.
他们把武器给我们 那就结了
They give us the armory and it's over.
你真想这样做吗？
Did you want this?
不想
No.
我之前崩溃了
I hit my limit.
我搞砸了
I... I screwed up.
然后我们就到了这一步
And here we are.
现在 恕我失陪
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要再去睡一会儿了
I'm just gonna sleep some more.
玛姬 她在门廊上
Maggie, hey. She's out on the porch.
你想谈什么 玛姬？
What do you need to talk about, Maggie?
今晚的会议
The meeting tonight.
玛姬 假如我们可以…
Maggie, if we could talk...
我想和所有人讨论发生的事
I want to talk to everyone about what happened
以及我们要对此采取什么措施
and what we need to do about it.
包括流放瑞克吗
If it includes sending Rick away,
那不会管用的
it's not gonna work.
这话是什么意思
Tell me what that means.
你让瑞克进来了
You let Rick in.
你让我们所有人进来了
You let all of us in.
你和我们谈过话
You talked to us.
你决定让我们留下
You decided.
如今你却想要将决定权
And now you want to put that decision
交到一群极度惊恐
on a group of very frightened people
而且不清楚来龙去脉的人手上
who might not have the whole story.
那可不是领袖该做的事
That's not leadership.
今晚只是一次讨论会
Tonight is just a forum.
让大家说说自己的想法
It's just for people to say their piece.
最终将由我来做出决定 一如既往
And I'll make the decision as I've done since the beginning.
他当时是触景生情
He was frustrated.
他所看见的 他所失去的
The things he's seen. The things he's lost.
我们大家失去的
The things we have all lost.
你们失去的吗？
The things you've lost?
我们失去的远比你多
We've lost so much more.
瑞克拿走了一把枪 并且用枪指着人
Rick took a gun and he pointed it at people.
他没有扣下扳机
He didn't pull the trigger.
那就是衡量标准吗？
That's a metric?
只要他没扣下扳机就行吗？
That he didn't pull the trigger?
- 是的 - 不是
- Yes. - No.
米琼恩阻止了他 迪安娜
Michonne stopped him, Deanna.
米琼恩出手了
Michonne did.
我要做我必须做的事 玛姬
I'm gonna do what I have to do, Maggie.
玛姬
Maggie.
听着 玛姬
Look, Maggie.
穴居人
The cavemen,
他们是游牧民
they were all nomads.
他们都死了
And they all died.
然后我们人类进化成现代人 活了下来
Then we evolved into this and we lived.
只有我们不再漂泊才能建立文明
Civilization starts when we stop running.
当我们开始群居之后
When we live together.
当我们不再随便杀人
When we stop sending people away
和流放人的时候
from the world and from each other.
我会这么告诉她
That's what I'm going to tell her.
我也会这么告诉所有人
That's what I'm going to tell everyone.
好吗？
Okay?
不久前有人经过这里
Somebody came through here a while ago.
如果见到他们 我们就撤回
If we see them, we hang back,
安装好话筒
Set up the mike,
盯梢窃听
watch and listen.
盯多久？
For how long?
直到了解情况
Until we know.
我们必须了解情况
We have to know.
你们以前流放过人吗？
You've sent people away?
是的
Yeah.
发生了什么
What happened?
很早的时候了
It was early on.
有三个人
It was three people.
两男一女
Two men and a woman.
戴维森是他们的头儿
Davidson was their leader.
非常聪明 也很强壮
Smart as hell, strong.
我以为他们适合这里
I thought they'd work out.
可惜不适合
They didn't.
我带他们进来 又不得不送走他们
I brought them in and I had to see them out.
所以我 艾登 尼古拉斯
So me, Aiden, and Nicholas,
我们开车把他们拉到很远
we drove them out far...
给了他们能撑一天的水和食物
Gave them a day's worth of food and water
然后扔下了他们
and left them.
他们就那么配合吗？
They just went?
我们把他们的枪拿走了
We had their guns.
所有的枪都在我们这里
We had all the guns.
我不能犯同样的错误了
I can't make that kind of mistake again.
醒醒
Wake up.
昨晚的事挺好的
It's good what happened last night.
障眼法
We have more cover now.
他们都以为你被抓到了 都结束了
All of them think you've been found out, that it's over.
你为什么不想让他们知道我们还有枪？
Why didn't you want to tell them we had more guns?
米琼恩阻止了你 她把你打晕了
Michonne stopped you. She knocked you out.
是我活该
Well, I deserved it.
你确实很傻
Well, it was stupid.
她依然站在我们这边 格伦也是
She's with us. Glenn is.
我没告诉他们枪的事是以防万一
I didn't tell them about the guns just in case.
我不想再说谎了
I don't want to lie anymore.
你说你不想夺权
You said you don't want to take this place.
而且你不想说谎？
And you don't want to lie?
亲爱的 鱼和熊掌不可兼得
Oh, sunshine, you don't get both.
他在干什么？
What's he doing?
是野韭菜
Wild leeks.
那混蛋知道如何防蚊虫叮咬
Son of a bitch knows about how to keep mosquitos off of him.
走吧
Come on.
你好 托宾
Hey, Tobin.
你好 瑞克
Hey, Rick.
- 你和她谈了？- 是的
- You met with her? - Yeah.
什么情况？
So what is it?
跟我们想的一样
It's what we thought.
我得跟大家谈谈
I'm gonna talk to people.
我得在开会前尽量多找人谈谈
I'll talk to everyone I can right up until.
我要努力解决这件事
I'm gonna try to solve this.
怎么了？
What?
我爱你
I love you.
我们会解决的
We're gonna work it out.
我知道的
I know it.
- 那边见 - 好的
- I'll see you there. - Yeah.
你真的不想带枪吗 神父？
Sure you don't want a gun, Father?
我只想去散会儿步
I just want a quick walk.
有上帝的庇护就足够了
The word of god is the only protection I need.
爸
Dad.
你没事吧？
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
我听说会议的事了
I heard about the meeting.
你留在家里
You're staying home.
现在这里就是了 是吧？
That's what it is now, right?
家？
Home?
是啊
Yeah.
他们需要我们
They need us.
没有我们他们必死
They'll die without us.
我恐怕要威胁他们其中一个人
I might have to threaten one of them.
我可能要杀掉他们其中一个人
I could have to kill one of them.
- 你不会的 - 有可能的
- You won't. - I might.
你必须告诉他们
You have to tell them.
昨晚我就告诉他们了
I told them last night.
他们必须听得进去才算数
You have to tell them so they can hear you.
我不知道他们能否听得进去
I don't know if they can.
你害怕这样吗？
Does that make you afraid?
为了他们好
Just for them.
你必须告诉他们
You have to tell them.
(戴尔·阿诺食品 水果蔬菜罐头)
我们把森林和道路都搜索了一遍
We checked the forest, we checked the roads.
我们找不到他了
We can't find him.
有时候就是会跟丢的
Sometimes they slip away. It happens.
但是…
But...
并不是每天都能碰到食品厂
You don't come across something like this every day.
如果我们去拿食物 就得放弃找他了
We do this now, it means we're giving up.
我们距家已经50英里了 该回去了
Home is 50 miles back. It's time to go.
你昨晚也看到了 外面有坏人
You saw it last night. There's bad people out here.
正因此我们才要继续寻找那些好人
That's why we ought to keep looking for the good ones.
我们需要更多的人 而且肯定会找到的
We need more people and we'll find them.
但找到以后 还得供应他们食物
But when we do, we'll need to feed them.
好吧
All right.
(如何把丰收带回家)
没想到我还能看到这种车牌
Wasn't sure I'd ever see one of these.
听着 我也不喜欢放弃
Hey, listen, I don't like giving up either,
但那个人穿着红色雨衣
but the guy is in a red poncho.
在一英里之外就可以看到
You can see him from a mile away.
(阿拉斯加州)
我们已经追了很远了
We've gone a lot of miles here.
都没看到他
No sign of him.
但是…
But...
我们要能带回去一车的罐头
if we come away with a trailer full of cans,
我觉得也不虚此行了
I'd say that's a good trip.
好了
Here we go.
这边
Over here!
快点
Come on!
- 不 - 快走
- No! - Come on.
快点 快啊
Come on! Go!
窗户能挡一阵子吧？
Glass will hold for a while, right?
或许吧
Maybe.
也许我们可以让它们忽视我们
Maybe we can make it so they can't see us.
过几个小时 总会有东西路过
In a couple hours, something will come by,
它们就会跟着走了
they'll follow it out.
车里应该有东西能挡住玻璃
There's got to be something in here we can use to block the view.
可以把座椅划开
We can cut up these seats.
(陷阱 坏人会来 别停留)
你他妈来干什么
What the hell are you doing?
你得去看看塔拉
You need to check on Tara.
是你治的她 你是医生 你得负责
You treated her. You're a surgeon. You need to do that.
出去
Get out.
我现在就能杀了你
I could kill you right now.
我可以的
I could.
我会的
I will.
然后谁会相信 我杀了你
And then who would believe I did it
是因为我不喜欢你呢？
because I didn't like you?
没人会信
No one.
他们会相信你试图伤害我
They'd believe you tried to hurt me.
肯定会信
Definitely believe that.
打我啊
Come at me.
不来吗？
No?
来吗？
Yeah?
不敢啊
No.
按这样下去 你还有机会
The way this has played out, you have a chance.
你住在这边
You're here.
你妻子住在那边
Your wife's there.
你是个渺小的懦夫
You're a small, weak nothing.
现在这世道
And with the world how it is,
你就更怂了
you're even weaker.
如果你路子走得对
Play your cards right,
或许你就不用死了
maybe you don't have to die.
你吃完把盘子洗干净
And I want my dish back clean when you're done.
这不是我家
This isn't my house.
This isn't my house!
你还是走吧
You should go.
我只是想来看看你
I just wanted to check on you.
你的眼睛
Your eye.
我拉他时被打的 不是你的错
He did it right when it was happening. It wasn't you.
不能让别人看见我们聊天
People shouldn't see us talking right now.
我不后悔做了那事
I'm not sorry I did it.
不管发生什么
No matter what happens
或是我不得不做什么
or what I have to do.
别转身 瑞克
Don't turn around, Rick.
你之前说的对
You were right.
怎么了？
What?
我出来是为了…
I came out here to...
逃离那个封闭的环境
not feel all closed up back there.
即便像现在这样
Even now,
我还是觉得要比
this still feels more like me...
待在那些屋子里自在
than back in them houses.
这挺不正常的 对吧？
That's pretty messed up, huh?
你在努力融入
You were trying.
我没得选
I had to.
不对
No, you didn't.
听着 我看见你和你的队伍在路上走
Listen, I saw you with your group out there on the road.
然后你一个人到了谷仓边
Then you went off on your own by the barn.
暴风雨来临
Storm hit
你把你的人带到了安全地
and you led your people to safety.
就因为这点
That was it.
我知道我得把你们都带回去
I knew I had to bring you people back.
你说的对
You were right.
我们本该继续寻找那个穿雨衣的人
We should have kept looking for that guy in the poncho.
我不应该放弃的
I shouldn't have given up.
你就没有
You didn't.
我出去
I'll go.
我把它们引开 你逃到围栏那里去
I'll lead them out. You make a break for the fence.
不不不
No, no, no.
这是我的错
This was my fault.
那不是在问你意见
It wasn't a question.
这也由不得你来决定
And this ain't your decision.
这不是任何人的错
It ain't nobody's fault.
先让我把这根烟抽完
Just let me finish my smoke first.
不
No.
你不用引开他们
You don't draw them away.
我们一起战斗
We fight.
一起到围栏那里 一起行动
We go for the fence. We do it together.
好吗 不管能不能活下来
All right? Whether we make it or not,
我们一起行动
we do it together.
我们必须一起
We have to.
好吧
All right.
- 准备好了吗？- 好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
数到三
We'll go on three.
一 二
One, two...
快点 快点过来
Come on. Come on, get in here.
刚刚真是…
That was...
谢谢
thank you.
我是亚伦 这是达里尔
I'm Aaron, this is Daryl.
我是摩根
Morgan.
为什么？
Why?
因为所有生命都是宝贵的 达里尔
Because all life is precious, Daryl.
设陷阱的那些人要来了
Whoever set that trap, they're coming.
但我… 我们有个好消息
But I have good news. We do.
离这里不远的地方有个社区
We have a community not too far from here.
有围墙 有电 而且很安全
Walls, electricity, it's safe.
- 如果你想加入我们 - 谢谢
- I...If you'd like to come join us - I thank you.
但我要去一个地方
But I'm on my way somewhere.
不过我迷路了 所以…
Fact is, I'm lost, so...
你能不能告诉我这里的位置
if you could tell me where we are.
(抱歉 我是个混蛋  去华盛顿吧  新世界需要瑞克·格兰姆斯)
我准备好了
I'm ready.
我一会儿再来吧
I'll ...come by later.
他睡着了
He's asleep.
他睡着了 坐吧
He's asleep. Sit.
下午好
Good afternoon.
她救了我的命
She saved my life.
她还让我醍醐灌顶
She also cracked open my gourd
理解了我未曾理解的一些事
to considering implications I hadn't.
我会利用这次机会抒发己见
I will remark about those at this time.
你把我们带到了这里
You got us here.
我只是编了一个弥天大谎
All I did was craft a top- shelf lie
让一个孔武而英勇的人能够发挥才能
to which a person with strength and heroism could apply their talents.
我觉得你当时也需要这个契机
My bet was you needed that.
我很感谢你
I thank you.
我很抱歉
I am sorry.
我对你的感谢和抱歉是等量的
And I mean both emphatically and in equal measure.
我…
I'm...
也很抱歉
sorry, too.
完全没必要
Utterly and completely unnecessary.
我差点杀了你
I almost killed you.
是啊 那倒是
Yes, there's that.
你回来了
You're back.
很好 我正想偷偷溜去参加会议
Good, just wanted to sneak off to the meeting.
你觉得我们晚些时候可以聊一下吗？
You think we could find some time to talk later?
聊聊艾登？
About Aiden?
我有些话想说
Just some things I need to say
但不知道可以找谁说
and I'm not sure who I can say them to.
我现在真的没有一个可以交心的人
I don't really have anyone here right now,
你应该明白我的意思吧
if you know what I mean.
再说吧
I'll see.
好的
Cool.
你能把门带上吗？
Can you get that?
- 好 - 谢谢
- Yeah. - Thank you.
瑞克
Rick.
你准备好了吗？
You ready?
卡萝尔 达里尔
Carol, Daryl,
和我…
and me...
我们一起计划的
we worked it out together.
卡萝尔从武器库拿了三把枪
Carol took three guns from the armory.
我还有一把 她手上也还有一把
I still have one, she still has one.
我们对你说谎是因为
We lied to you because
我不知道你会如何反应
I wasn't sure how you'd take it,
你会做出什么事
what you'd do.
你觉得我会试图阻止你吗？
You think I'd try to stop you?
你的确打了我的头啊
Well, you did hit me over the head.
那是为你好 不是为他们
That was for you, not them.
我之前害怕你会劝我放弃
I was afraid you'd talk me out of it.
你有可能这样做
You could've.
我们不需要他们
We don't need them here.
我也不需要我的刀
I don't need my sword.
我觉得你能想出办法的
I think you can find a way.
我们可以想出办法的
We can find a way.
如果我们想不出…
And if we don't...
我依然追随你
I'm still with you.
肯定会出事
Something's gonna happen.
但别主动惹事
Just don't make something happen.
别太久了
Don't be too long.
很快你就会发现
You're gonna find yourself in a place
生活又恢复原状了
where it's like how it used to be.
如果你放弃了太多人性
And if you let too much go along the way,
那是不行的
that's not gonna work.
因为你会重回现实世界
Because you're gonna be back in the real world.
这就是现实世界 鲍勃
This is the real world, Bob.
不 这是一场噩梦
Nah, this is a nightmare.
迟早会醒的
And nightmares end.
我来到这里…
I came here...
是因为我不知道该怎么办才好
because I don't... I don't know what to do.
我失去理智了
I'm losing my head.
你能帮我吗？
Can you help me?
不能
No.
我们开始吧
We're going to start.
可以再等等吗？
Can we wait?
还有人会来的
There's still people coming.
格伦 瑞克
Glenn, Rick.
我们这就开始
We're going to start.
已经天黑了
It's already dark.
我们要谈谈最近发生的事
We're going to talk about what happened.
不谈打架的事  也不谈前因后果
Not the fight. Not what precipitated it.
我们正在处理那事
We're dealing with that.
我们要谈谈我们的一位治安官
We're going to talk about one of our constables,
瑞克·格兰姆斯
Rick Grimes.
我们要谈谈
We're going to talk about
他从武器库偷了一把手枪的事
how he had a pistol he stole from the armory,
他竟然拿枪对着自己人
about how he pointed it at people.
我们还要谈谈他之前说过的一些话
And we're going to talk about what he said.
我也希望他此刻能在这里
I was hoping he'd be here.
她说过他会来的
She said he's coming.
我相信他会来的
I'm sure he'll be here.
我也相信我们一定能好好解决这事的
And I'm sure we can work this all out.
我觉得我想死
I think I want to die.
你怎么会不想死呢？
Why wouldn't you want to die?
你根本不配来这里
You don't deserve to be here.
你的所作所为 是无法抹除的
What you did can never be undone.
死人没有选择权 但你做出的那些选择
The dead don't choose, but the choices you made,
你竟然牺牲了自己的…
how you sacrificed your own...
我知道你在干什么
I know what you're doing.
鲍勃当时被截肢了
Bob was mutilated.
被吃了
Consumed.
你的罪孽 让他被毁了
Destroyed because of your sins.
别说了
Stop it.
你哥哥觉得那事与他无关
Your brother felt he was apart from it.
但他其实脱不了干系
He was a part of it.
他不配来这里
He didn't deserve to be here.
- 你也不配 - 住嘴 住嘴
- You don't! - Stop it! Stop it!
以前在外面挣扎求生
And after being out there
现在又得接受另一种生活方式
and then not being how you were out there...
这会把人逼疯的
It can drive you crazy.
瑞克只是希望家人能活下来
Rick just wants his family to live.
他希望你们都能活下来
He wants all of you to live.
他现在的样子
Who he is
就是你们以后的样子…
is who you're gonna be...
如果你们走运的话
If you're lucky.
瑞克·格兰姆斯一次又一次地救过我的命
Rick Grimes saved my life over and over.
外面有很多很可怕的人
There's terrifying people out there.
他从他们手中把我救出来
And he rescued me from them.
像我这样的人
People like me,
像我们这样的人
People like us
需要像他那样的人
Need people like him.
我知道昨晚发生的事很吓人
I know what happened last night was scary.
我相信他一定深感抱歉
And I'm sure he's sorry for that.
但或许我们应该听进去他说的话
But maybe we should listen to what he was saying.
简而言之…
Simply put...
可怕的屁事有很多 而你们屁也不知道
There is a vast ocean of shit that you people don't know shit about.
瑞克对那些可怕的屁事了如指掌…
Rick knows every fine grain of said shit...
甚至远不止于此
And then some.
- 拜托不要 - 嘘
- Please don't. - Shh.
- 不要 - 它们会听见的
- No. - They'll hear you.
那样重置需要更久
It'll take longer to reset it.
别乱动
Just be still.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
我父亲敬重瑞克·格兰姆斯
My father respected Rick Grimes.
瑞克也是一位父亲
Rick is a father, too.
他有一颗善良的心
He's a man with a good heart
他对做过的坏事
who feels the things he does,
会感到愧疚
the things he has to do.
而我们这些
And all of us
来到这里前就在一起的人
who were together before this place,
不管我们是何时相遇的
no matter when we found each other,
我们现在都是一家人
We're family now.
这全靠瑞克
Rick started that.
你阻止不了
And you won't stop it.
你做不到
You can't.
你也不想做
And you don't want to.
这个社区 你们这些人…
This community, you people...
那个大家庭…
That family...
你们也想加入的
You want to be a part of it, too.
在其他人发言之前
Before we hear from anyone else, I...
我想本着透明的原则 分享一件事
I would like to share something in the spirit of transparency.
加百利神父前天来找过我
Father Gabriel came to see me the day before yesterday
他说我们不能信任
And he said our new arrivals
这些新人
can't be trusted,
他们很危险
That they were dangerous,
他们会把自己的利益放在社区之前
that they would put themselves before this community.
不到一天之后
And not one day later,
瑞克就证实了加百利神父
Rick seemed to demonstrate all the things
所说的一切
Father Gabriel said.
我希望加百利今晚也在场
I had hoped Gabriel would be here tonight.
我没看见他 迪安娜
I don't see him here, Deanna.
所以你只是在口头转述他的话
So you're just saying what someone said.
你录下他的话了吗？
Did you tape him?
- 他不在 - 瑞克也不在
- He's not here. - Neither is Rick.
失陪了
Excuse me.
诺亚是被你害死的
Noah died because of you.
我想告诉你事实 教你怎么做
And I tried to tell you how it is, how it has to be
你却想杀我？
and you try to kill me?
我只想保护我的家人
I just want to keep my family safe.
你知道吗？我都不知道这意味着什么了
You know? And I don't even know what that means anymore,
但是如果这意味着我们要流放…
but if it means that we've got to get rid of...
我当时惊慌了 我惊慌了
I was scared. I was scared.
- 我不适应外面 - 闭嘴
- I don't belong out here. - Shut up.
我惊慌了 我惊慌了
I was scared. I was just scared.
- 闭嘴 - 我不…
- Shut up. - I don't...
- 我不适应… - 闭嘴
- I don't belong... - Shut up!
我不适应外面
I don't belong out here.
我不
I don't.
闭嘴
Shut up.
开枪吧
Do it.
萨沙
Sasha.
你应该让她开枪
You should let her.
他们死了
They died.
他们都因我而死
They all died because of me.
确实如此
They did.
门口没有一个警卫
There wasn't a guard on the gate.
门大开着
It was open.
我让加百利关上了
I asked Gabriel to close it.
快去
Go.
行尸不是我带进来的
I didn't bring it in.
是它们自己进来的
It got inside on its own.
它们总会进来…
They always will...
不管是死人还是活人
The dead and the living,
因为我们在里面
because we're in here.
外面的那些家伙
And the ones out there...
会跟着我们
They'll hunt us.
会找到我们
They'll find us.
会试着利用我们
They'll try to use us.
会试着杀掉我们
They'll try to kill us.
但是我们会杀了它/他们
But we'll kill them.
我们能活下去 我会教你们
We'll survive. I'll show you how.
我之前在想…
You know, I was thinking...
我要杀你们多少人
I was thinking how many of you do I have to kill
才能救你们？
to save your lives?
但我不会那样做了
But I'm not gonna do that.
你们必须做出改变
You're gonna change.
我对昨晚的话不后悔
I'm not sorry for what I said last night.
我后悔的是没有早说
I'm sorry for not saying it sooner.
你们没准备好
You're not ready,
但是你们必须准备好
but you have to be.
现在就得准备好
Right now, you have to be.
运气会到头的
Luck runs out.
你不是我们的一员 你不是我们的一员
You're not one of us. You're not one of us!
皮特 别这样做
Pete, you don't want to do this.
- 别靠近我 雷吉 - 皮特 住手
Get the hell away from me, Reg. Pete, just stop.
- 闪开 - 雷吉
Get away from me. Reg. Reg.
- 闪开 闪开 - 先别动手
- Get away. Get away! - not now.
- 皮特 住手 皮特 - 闪开
- Now, Pete, stop. Pete... - Get away!
- 不 - 不
- No, no! - Oh, no, no!
- 都怪他 - 闭嘴
- This is him! - Shut up!
- 都怪他 - 上帝啊
- This is him! - Oh, god!
亲爱的 亲爱的
Oh, my love. My love, my love.
不 亲爱的 不
no, my love, no.
不 亲爱的
No, my love.
怪他
It's him!
都怪他
This is him!
瑞克…
Rick...
动手
Do it.
瑞克？
Rick?